Inventory of the Devin A. Garrity papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Subject File, 1919-1980
  - Princeton University
    - Survey, 1948 May-1959 January
      - Alumni, 1952 November-1953 June (Box-folder 1: 8)
      - Wilcox, 1952 November-1953 September (Box-folder 1: 7)
      - Accounting, 1953 May-June (Box-folder 1: 3)
    - Princeton and Dickinson College materials, 1948 July-1950 February (Box-folder 1: 1)
    - Education, "The Educational Reviewer,", 1949 October-1953 May (Box-folder 2: 4)
    - Princeton Society Meeting 6 November 1953, 1952 December-1953 August (Box-folder 1: 2)
      Includes related materials.
    - Assorted materials, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Political issues
    - Labor, communism, press, and civil liberties, 1948 April-1954 July (Box-folder 22: 9)
    - Press and censorship, 1951 July-1956 September (Box-folder 33: 7)
      Includes correspondence, newsletters, and articles.
    - ACLU, book burning, and censorship, 1953 May-September (Box-folder 19: 5)
      Includes magazine articles and newspaper clippings.
    - Joe McCarthy, 1953 July-1958 July (Box-folder 29: 1)
      Includes articles, pamphlets, and newspaper clippings.
    - Civil rights movement, 1966 March-1968 May (Box-folder 11: 9)
      Includes newspaper clippings.
    - American activist, 1971 July-1979 November (Box-folder 49: 3)
      Includes correspondence, text, and pamphlets.
    - Conservative Political Action Conference and Young Americans for Freedom, 1971 August-1976 February (Box-folder 49: 4-6)
      Includes correspondence and records.
    - American opinion, John Birch Society, 1972 November-1976 February (Box-folder 50: 13)
    - Phyllis Schlafly vs. equal rights amendment, 1975 December-1976 January (Box-folder 49: 7)
      Includes articles, and correspondence.
    - Conservative directory and issues, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 35: 11)
      Includes pamphlets, newsletters, and clippings.
    - American opinion, John Birch Society, 1976 March-1980 August (Box-folder 48: 11)
      Includes correspondence and newsletters.
  - Post Civil War Spain
    - "The Friends of the Spanish Republic, Committee for Democratic Spain,", 1945 April-1946 October (Box-folder 35: 3)
    - Spain, "Pros and Cons of Franco" and the McMahon affair, 1946 July-1958 July (Box-folder 35: 4)
      Includes interview transcripts, correspondence, and articles.
    - Franco, 1947 March-1950 January (Box-folder 35: 2)
      Includes notes, Life articles, and newsletters.
  - Science
    - Science and mechanics, 1956 April-1966 June (Box-folder 21: 1)
      Includes magazines and correspondence.
    - Science and healing, 1973 (Box-folder 21: 4)
      Includes essays and articles.
  - Spirituality and faith
    - "Guide to Catholic Europe,", undated (Box-folder 17: 4-6)
      Includes photographs and descriptions, maps, and manuscript.
    - "Spiritism And Religion," The Homiletic Monthly and Pastoral Review, Everybody's Magazine, 1919 July-1922 June (Box-folder 10: 8)
    - "Christianity and Judaism in Trouble,", 1969 January-1971 October (Box-folder 17: 9)
  - UFOs
    - Salisbury, 1973 August-1979 July (Box-folder 37: 7)
    - Dr. X, 1973 October-November (Box-folder 43: 8)
- Scrapbooks, 1915-1947
  - Chant, English, Franco, etc., 1915 September-1948 September (Box-folder 52: 2)
  - "War and the Poet,", 1925 October-1947 February (Box-folder 52: 1)
  - Assorted articles, pictures, and paintings, 1939 December-1960 November (Box-folder 52: 3)
  - "Out Of Debt Out Of Danger,", 1943 March-September (Box-folder 3: 4)
  - "Pay Dirt,", 1945 October-1947 August (Box-folder 3: 1)
  - Post Civil War Spain, 1946 September-December (Box-folder 3: 3)
- Motion Picture Films, undated (Box shelf)
  16mm film.
  - "Answers for Americans"
    Contains episodes of the television program "Answers to Americans," which presented a conservative and anti-communist viewpoint. Garrity was a frequent panelist on the program.
    - "#5A" (2 copies) (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#9" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#9A" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#10A" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#11A" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#12A" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#13A" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#15A" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#16A" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#17A" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#19A" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#22A" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#23A" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#24A" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#25A" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#27A" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#28A" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#29A" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#30A" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#31A" (Film shelf shelf)
    - "#34A" (Film shelf shelf)
  - Unidentified (7 film reels) (Film shelf shelf)